Finding Aid for Ira W. Butterfield (1915-1995) Papers 1875-1990
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Archaeology
  - Correspondence (Box 10)
    - Maxwell, Moreau S., 1968-1972 (Box 10)
    - Passenger, Ruth W., 1955-1959 (Box 10)
    - Payne, James, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
    - Simons, Don, 1986-1992 (Box 10)
    - Thompson, Harold, 1970-1978 (Box 10)
    - Tracy, Oscar, 1962-1965 (Box 10)
    - Voss, Jerry, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Weston, Don, 1972-1975 (Box 10)
    - General, 1955-1978 (Box 10)
  - Sanilac Petroglyphs
    - General, 1958-1985 (Box 10)
    - Application to Earhart Foundation, 1967 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1986 (Box 10)
    - Conservation Department Information, 1965-1980 (Box 10)
    - Exhibits and Documents, circa 1967 (Box 10)
    - Photographs
      - 1965, 1978 (Box 10)
      - undated (Box 10)
    - Early Group Activities, 1941-1970 (Box 10)
- Photographs
  The final series is Photographs. Included are 11 black and white positive portraits. The poses include Ira Butterfield in his judicial robes and law library, probably taken with a view towards using them in his campaign literature.
  - Portraits of Butterfield (Box 10)